Come on, guys. Hurry up.
The audition is in three hours.
Why did we have to get up at 6:00?
-Do you think Take That slept until noon?
-I'm so tired.
'Cause someone watched
the Grammys yesterday.
-Yes.
-It was a group decision.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Exactly!
-Actually, where's Oli?
-Good question.
-There he is.
-Morning.
-Sorry, there was a long lineup.
-You were flirting with that girl again.
-I was not. She was flirting with me.
-Yeah, sure.
Oh, man, no pink sprinkles.
-They're Peter's favorite.
-Sorry, they were sold out.
Hopefully, he's in a good mood.
Sorry, Peter. No pink sprinkles today.
Thank you.
-Come on, guys.
-Yes, all right.
Let's stop whining
and pull ourselves together.
Let's really crank up the bass
at rehearsal.
That's the right attitude.
-Sleep is overrated.
-You're such a weirdo.
All of this time
Make it all make sense
I'm going round and round
in circles again
It's a cataclysmic ride into the unknown
Impossible to synchronize
But let's go
All of these lights can we recompare
I'm going higher and higher
From Earth into space
It's an existential search
In how it hurts
Stop, no, no.
Guys!
-What's wrong?
-We can't perform the song like this.
What do you mean?
Something's missing.
The song lacks magic. It's got nothing.
-Not again, bro.
-Ben, the showcase is coming up.
-We need to make some progress.
-Guys, these lyrics. Seriously.
We keep starting over.
-Bro, the lyrics are great.
-No, Matteo!
Just give me a few minutes, okay?
Unbelievable.
-Let's just take a break.
-Any moment now…
If we start all over again now
and do everything from scratch…
All the lyrics, the choreo, the chords.
How many times has it been this month?
We can't keep scrapping the song
and starting from scratch.
He's writing in his notebook again.
Nothing's gonna come of it.
-He's changing everything.
-I don't get it.
-Hi there.
-Hi.
-It's getting serious now, isn't it?
-Yes. Totally.
If you mess up now, then you don't stand
a chance later in front of the pros.
Yes.
Hi, Sky. What's up?
Hi.
Hi, Sky.
-Your bag, Ben.
-How's the song coming along?
-I'm a little nervous.
-How are things, Sky?
All good, and you?
-Ready to wow them all?
-We'll see.
100%.
How did Matteo describe your voice again?
Like if Beyoncé and DaBaby
had a love child.
Debbie Harry, not DaBaby.
Oh, God.
Seriously.
-I'll go run through the lyrics again.
-Totally.
-You're gonna do great.
-Good luck.
Later, guys.
-Good morning.
-Are you stupid?
Morning.
-Good morning, everyone.
-Morning.
The showcase is in a few days, so now's
your chance to show what you've got.
Remember, several music professionals
will be there.
-Wait, Ms. Robinson is in Synk?
-She has more Grammys than Taylor Swift.
They're not playing around.
Yeah, bro.
Working with her would be so wild.
They want to see artists
who are ready to give it their all.
Once you're on stage,
there are no more excuses.
-Okay?
-Okay.
I can see you in the corner of the room
When you're near
My heart beats out of tune
Oh, I wish you'd notice
The way I light up, too
Somewhere around
A world of endless grace
I'm more than just a face
Just another face
Skyler.
Skyler, wait.
-Just forget it.
-Please wait.
I'm sorry.
I had to work on the lyrics,
and the bridge isn't quite right yet.
-The boys don't understand that I…
-Ben.
It's okay.
It's just, your world, this perfectionism…
I'm done.
That's it for us.
I hope that you will feel
something again one day.
But…
Come on, we're up.
Ben!
Come on.
Okay. Our song is unfortunately
not quite finished yet.
That's right,
but it will be ready for the showcase.
Are you okay?
We are 5G,
and this is "Gotta Make It Work."
I hope that you will feel
something again one day.
Hey, what's going on?
-Ben.
-Where are you going?
Ben?
Come on, dude.
Let us at least talk to you.
Just chill out.
You just had a little blackout.
-It happens.
-You don't get it.
-That's your problem exactly. You're…
-Just go away!
That's it, guys. I'm out.
Come on, guys. Leave him be.
This sucks.
Come on, guys.
-It is still not working.
-Damn it.
-How will we do this without him?
-We have to be honest with ourselves.
It doesn't work without him. Fact.
We can't just throw it all away now.
Then this will all have been for nothing.
-Let's try again.
-You, I…
-I need a break first.
-Me, too.
Well, this sucks.
A follower just sent me
a link to a TikTok page.
With these really cool
vintage '90s B-sides.
-Really? Your solution is old B-sides?
-Listen to it. It's awesome.
I still hear you
In the midnight air
Your voice is the wind
It's the sound
Of a whispered prayer
Honestly, it's way cooler
than anything we're doing right now.
-How do you make something like that?
-I wish I knew.
Hey, losers!
What do you want, Alisha?
Aren't you called 5G?
-So why are there only 4Gs?
-Stop staring!
-Shut up, Oli.
-You're nothing without Ben.
Well, guys, she's not wrong.
Chris.
What's going on here?
The big Heartville University showcase
is scheduled for tonight.
Who will blow the jury away?
Who will go down in music history?
But this date also brings up
some bad memories for Heartville.
Thirty years ago, on June 6, 1995,
at exactly 6:00 p.m.,
-the elevator cable snapped…
-Today is the showcase. We need you.
-Please call.
-…and Daniel Weber died.
Out of respect, the elevator
was not used for decades,
but was recently put back into service.
A simple brass plaque commemorates this…
Hopefully, his dad will be done
lecturing him soon. We gotta go.
Yeah, man.
You said that already. One could argue…
-Bye, Dad.
-Bye, darling.
Bye. Ciao, Matteo.
-Bye… Bye.
-…but it keeps happening.
"Ciao, Matteo"?
What did I say about rehearsing here?
Yes. I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
Never mind.
You won't have time for that anyway.
Do you know why?
You've been accepted at Heartville.
To study medicine.
Are you happy?
Yes, but the year isn't over yet.
Chris.
I know how much music
and all of this means to you, but…
What if it doesn't work out?
This is a safe prospect.
I don't want you to throw this away
and regret it later. Do you understand?
Then I just have to make sure
that it does go somewhere.
You're…
When I was young, I never had
garbage like that in my head.
Please, don't start that again.
I have to go.
Your interview with Dr. Mehackerberg
is this afternoon.
Yes.
-Be on time.
-Yes.
-What's up?
-Nothing.
He's just lecturing me again.
We've invited some important people.
I'm delighted…
If you're late again, you're out.
And your recent performance…
Sorry, we were just rehearsing.
Ms. Robinson hates lateness.
Ms. Robinson?
She'll be at the showcase.
-Guys, we're so screwed.
-Now what?
-We really need to go for it.
-Let's go.
Sure, go. It's not like we're in class.
-Are you crazy?
-Ben, you have to come with us now.
-I don't have to do anything.
-Ms. Robinson is coming to the showcase.
So what?
"So what?" This is our chance.
We can't do this without you.
-It's not my problem anymore.
-Yes, it is, Ben.
We built this together. It's about us.
Are you crazy?
You want to throw it all away?
-All of our songs?
-Give it to me.
Just listen to us. What's wrong with you?
I already told you. I'm done.
-You're the reason we even started.
-Ben…
Come on, bro! It's pointless without you.
Ben, running away isn't a solution.
-Wait.
-What the hell is this?
-Without you, we can forget about 5G.
-You're better off without me.
You were just taking a break, right?
A break? This is no longer a break.
Bro…
Okay.
You've convinced me.
-Really?
-No.
Forget it, dude. We're going
to the rehearsal room now, okay?
Cut the crap, okay?
Guys, just chill.
Hey.
Seriously, that's enough.
And then more stupid lies
It's the song from this morning.
Everyone's trying to figure out
who sings it.
I still hear you
In the midnight air
Don't you feel it, too?
Let's just continue together.
I can't.
And then like ghosts
I still hear you
In the midnight air
Your voice is the wind
It's the sound
Of a whispered prayer
And then like ghosts
Just a memory
What was that?
Is everyone all right?
Is it me, or does something
look weird here?
Oh, my God, guys.
My phone. It was at 70%,
and now it's not working at all.
-Mine's not working either.
-Same.
-We're in hell.
-How did you come to that conclusion?
-In heaven, my phone would still work.
-Yes, that's a bug.
This can't be happening.
I'll tell you what can't be happening,
that you're all in my way.
Hi.
Sorry, I didn't do it on purpose.
-Hey.
-Just ignore them.
They can't control their balls.
It's fine. Everything's okay. All good.
-What are you doing here?
-We're students here.
Really? I've never seen you before.
-You either.
-MJ?
-I was looking for you. We'll be late.
-Yeah, okay. Just chill.
-This is…
-Hi. Oli.
-Chris.
-Jonas.
Matteo.
Ben.
-I'm pleased to meet you.
-Well, that makes one of us.
Listen, we have to go.
Science club is about to start.
Okay, just a sec. Did you hear
about the house party tonight?
I'll give you the address.
Yes, so maybe…
-See you later?
-Yes, see you later. Or some other time.
If you keep drooling,
I'll have to get you a bucket.
Guys?
What's up?
-What the hell?
-This has got to be a joke, right?
It has to be a joke.
-This can't be real.
-Shit!
No!
How the hell did we end up in 1995?
-Shit!
-I don't know either! Damn!
-Come on. Get in.
-This is just a bad dream.
Let's go up, then down again.
It'll be back to normal.
-Maybe they're hipsters.
-I think it worked.
-No, shit.
-Damn!
Damn, this can't be happening.
Is this a dream or something?
Oh, no!
-Again.
-Okay, come on.
-What? No.
-This can't be happening!
This sucks.
No!
Shit!
Let's try it again. Come on.
Come on, guys. Let's go.
Are there any other elevators here?
That can travel through time?
Was that a yes or a no?
"Nothing you hear will show you the way."
"Only what remains will."
"Silent and abundant."
"What sounds devoid of truth
moves nothing forward."
"And nothing will succeed."
Ben? Come on.
Hey!
Guys, how do we get back to our time?
No idea.
Wait, is that a telephone?
It's a telephone, right?
Maybe we can call someone.
Do you remember any phone numbers?
-No.
-I don't know any, either.
I only know 911.
-No.
-Okay.
What's this?
-The instruction manual.
-No, that can't be it.
Those are names
and those are phone numbers.
-What? Just like that in public?
-Yes. Look.
What about privacy laws?
Check if my grandma is in there.
We could call her.
Great idea. And what will you tell her?
"Hey, I'm your grandchild
from the future."
"I'd like to go back.
I'm on campus. Can you pick me up?"
Yes, exactly. Back to the Future.
What if it's just like that movie?
There was this crazy scientist.
That girl earlier was wearing
a science club T-shirt.
Her friend flirted with Ben.
She didn't flirt with me.
-Did she?
-She must know a professor
who can help us to get back home.
You're saying
that we need to find a professor
who is building a time machine
out of a DeLorean
that only works if lightning strikes
the town hall clock at 10:04 p.m.
and powers the DeLorean
with 1.21 gigawatts via the power line,
at exactly 88 miles per hour, by the way,
so that we travel through time
and get back to the future
like Michael J. Fox did
in his iconic role?
Yes.
Okay.
Hey, Chris. Isn't this is your address?
Looks like a decent party.
Are you stupid?
What does he want?
-What a jerk.
-Okay, come on. Let's go.
-What should I do if I see my dad?
-That's right.
As we know from Back to the Future,
we mustn't interfere with the past.
So, when you see your dad,
don't talk to him.
What if he recognizes me?
-You haven't even been born yet.
-Oh, yeah, that's right.
As long as we don't prevent our parents
from meeting, it should be okay, right?
Jonas is absolutely right.
Everything we do here
can change the space-time continuum.
Nice camera.
There could be dire consequences.
-"Space-time continuum"?
-Yes.
-What consequences?
-No idea.
This might come as a surprise,
but I've never time traveled before.
-Yes, okay. Fair.
-What is he doing?
-So, you can't swipe?
-Well, you swiped it from me.
My father won't even let us rehearse here,
and he does stuff like this.
-Unbelievable.
-Oli, come on.
Sorry, he talks first and thinks later.
Okay. Just let me know
when the thinking has started.
Okay, one more time for everyone.
If we want to get back, remember this.
We don't get involved with anyone
and remain inconspicuous.
-About getting "involved"…
-Don't make out with anyone, Oli.
-Hey, guys.
-I was just asking.
-There's the girl from the science club.
-Is nobody listening to me?
Hey, Jamie, MJ, come over here.
Next round, you two against the two of us.
And if you win,
I'll lend you Tekken for a month?
I already made a copy of Tekken.
We'd rather have your time slot
for the exam tomorrow.
No way.
Looks like someone's scared. Right, MJ?
-Yes!
-What do we get if we win?
You'll win Mary Jane's
exclusive Veruca Salt T-shirt.
-Absolutely not.
-Only if she takes it off right here.
-Okay, deal.
-Deal? Are you crazy?
-Hey.
-He won't win anyway.
Oh, you made it.
Even without Google Maps.
Without a map.
You're in the science club, right?
-What do you want?
-I just have a quick question.
Ten seconds.
Do you have a professor
who has a passion for…
Time travel?
And the cat's in the cradle
and the silver spoon
Little boy blue and the man in the moon
"When you coming home, Dad?"
"I don't know when"
"We'll have a good time then"
"You know we'll be together then"
-That was really great, Arno.
-Yeah, dude.
Do I know you?
-Theoretically, it's possible, but…
-Not tonight.
-We need beer.
-I'll get it. Can you hold my bag?
-Yes, sure.
-And, Chad? You've lost something.
Loser.
-Loser!
-Oh, wow.
Why doesn't she study music,
if she can sing that well?
You shouldn't study it at all.
Is there anything besides beer?
What would the gentleman like then?
Sex on the Beach?
At least invite me to dinner first.
I…
You play the guitar?
-Crazy.
-I play the guitar.
Yes.
-Do you play the guitar as well?
-Yes.
If you'd like,
we could jam together sometime.
Yes, sure. That would be great.
Right now… It's just not the right time.
-Sorry.
-Totally. Sure.
-I totally understand.
-Cool.
Your cocktail is ready.
You just need a straw.
They're in this drawer.
Oh, shit, what happened? Let me see.
-You need a band-aid.
-It's fine. Chris can take care of it.
There's a first-aid kit upstairs.
Who's Chris? How… do you know that?
There's always a first-aid kit upstairs.
Okay, let's go upstairs.
Okay.
Thanks, MJ.
Don't forget to breathe.
The station is on 95.6.
Bullshit. It's always been on 95.9.
It's Submission Hour.
Sorry. Hey, what's going on?
-It's Submission Hour?
-What's that?
Are you serious? Campus Radio plays songs
submitted by students once a week.
It's always so cool.
Hi, guys. Welcome to Submission Hour.
Today we're playing…
-Kira, hi. Cool name.
-Thanks. Nice to meet you.
-Daniel?
-Yes?
Let him take a hit, too.
Sure.
Daniel Weber?
Yes?
I think you'll survive.
That's a shame. I was already expecting
to make an epic exit.
Yes. I'm sorry about that.
No heroic death for you.
Are you studying medicine?
Or… do you have a secret double life
as a campus paramedic?
I'm studying computer science.
-And you?
-It's complicated.
Okay.
What's "Veruca Salt"?
Are you serious?
It's just the best band ever.
-That nobody knows?
-It doesn't make them any less good.
It's alternative rock.
American Thighs is a masterpiece.
I prefer pop music.
-Like New Kids On The Block?
-Don't trash pop music, okay?
I like it more complex.
Pop always has the same four chords.
C major, G major, A minor, and F major.
Just not that great.
-Right?
-You can't be serious.
"God Only Knows" has
an amazing chord progression.
And why does a computer science student
know so much about chords?
Why does a 20-year-old
listen to The Beach Boys?
A 20-year-old
who has a clue about good music.
And what exactly makes music good for you?
Well, when it's just perfect.
When everything is in the right place.
And for you?
When it gets to you
before you can think about it.
Jamie?
Take it off.
Not you, her!
-MJ, you have to take your clothes off.
-What?
Yes, your T-shirt. The Veruca Salt shirt.
-A deal's a deal.
-Shit.
I totally forgot about the game.
Jamie, I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. I didn't win, but I…
-You just need to take the shirt off…
-No.
Jamie, are you okay?
-Maybe I'll see you tomorrow?
-I don't know yet.
Are you leaving tomorrow?
I don't know that either.
Dude!
Okay, whatever.
I have to take care of my friend.
We also need to…
Because of the exam tomorrow. The thingy.
-Bye, Chad.
-Yes.
-Ciao.
-Bye.
It's all good, big guy.
And down we go!
Okay, guys. This next one
will blow you away. Listen up…
You can't ever take an elevator again.
-Of course.
-I'm serious.
And then like ghosts
Just a memory
Drift through the night, through the dark
Where we used to be
Dust and coffee rings…
It's the song from the elevator.
On the windowsill
Proof of the nights
We used to sit there still
Do you know the title of this song?
And who sings it?
-No?
-No idea.
Hey, guys!
Hey, there's Oli.
I think he wants us to join him.
Brilliant deduction.
-Come here!
-Oli, don't be an ass.
I still hear you
In the midnight air
Well?
Don't you recognize it?
-It's the song from the elevator.
-Exactly.
I was playing it
when the time travel happened.
Guys, it can't be a coincidence.
You think we ended up here
because of the song? That's impossible.
Okay, and you're a time travel expert now?
-No, but it just can't be.
-In most time travel movies,
you must exactly recreate
what you did to get back home.
Basically, we need to find this song.
Campus Radio must have a copy of it.
And then we'll go into the elevator
and play the song…
…like we did before.
And that will take us back to the future.
That's nonsense.
I think this is about something else.
I think we're here to convince my dad
to let me continue with music.
Who's in favor of finding the song
and going back to the elevator?
-Yes.
-Let me do some more research.
-Nothing else really makes any sense.
-Where is Oli going?
-What's up? All good?
Look at how much fun he's having.
This our only chance ever
to experience a real '90s party.
Let's just have a good time.
-Yes, but…
-Hey, bro.
Chris is right.
Just think of it… as research.
Let's get some breakfast.
I'll check the kitchen.
I don't know what's worse.
My hangover, or the fact
that we're still stuck in 1995.
Guys, you'll never guess
what happened to me yesterday.
I tried to save Daniel Weber.
-Who?
-The guy from the plaque?
No elevators, okay?
-Wait, when did the elevator crash again?
-It's on the plaque.
On June 6th, 1995.
-And what's today's date?
-June 6th.
The elevator was destroyed in the crash.
That means if we can't get back
before the accident…
-Then we'll be stuck here forever.
-Shit.
What time did it crash?
-After the last lecture.
-So, around 6:00 p.m.?
That means we have eight hours
to find the song.
-How do you know the time?
-I borrowed a watch from Chris's house.
-Borrowed?
-Yes.
Well, guys…
-Where do we start?
-I have an idea.
-Hi.
-Hello.
Hey! How are you?
-Have you come to steal my camera again?
-I gave it back to you.
Could you tell us where we can find
the Campus Radio host?
-We're big fans.
-Huge fans.
-Yes.
Crazy sound, right? Jesus Christ!
This is not a song, it's a wrecking ball.
It's as if Blondie
and The Clash had a baby.
Come on!
Damn it.
What a load of crap.
Sorry for the interruption.
As always, everything is fine.
My name is Marty
and you're listening to Heart Beat.
-Hi.
-Oh, no, guys. Seriously?
Olivia, when I said
I needed some new interns,
I didn't mean boys.
When will we get some girls in here?
-Nothing personal, Olivia.
-It's so weird.
Why don't young women want to work
with a 40-year-old loser
who's still around
ten years after graduating?
-Hey!
-You're a creep.
I'm not a creep.
-We're just here about a song…
-Your name is Olivia?
-Do you want to know my name?
-No, I don't.
-How did the song go?
-It was like…
Yes, that song was the bomb.
Exactly. We need it please.
Do you have the tape?
That's not possible.
-Why?
-It was stolen.
Breakup song. They must have regretted
submitting it. Happens a lot.
-But, hey, that's a great song.
-Stolen? Who stole it?
-Do you have cameras here?
-Cameras? Yes, of course.
Everywhere. Can't you see them?
The forensic team is currently
analyzing the fingerprints.
There must be a list showing
who comes in and out.
Listen, who are you guys anyway?
-A film crew.
-Yes, we're filming a documentary.
We're looking for new music stars.
-A documentary team without a camera?
-We're still doing research.
-Can you tell us who submitted it?
-There was something on the tape, but…
No idea, I can't remember.
Can you close the door on your way out?
Shit.
Yes, okay.
Thanks.
I just recalled
what was written on the tape.
"Charlie!"
Yes, that's it. "Charlie C."
-"Charlie C."
-Okay. Cool.
-Thanks.
Okay, Oli. You get Charlie C.'s file.
-Then we'll know who wrote the song.
-Okay.
I'll send it to you. Yes.
-Bye.
I'm here to pick up my transcript.
-Name?
-Charlie.
And the last name?
Charlie C.
Do it.
-Hello?
-Charlie C. Well, my last name…
Here we go, buddy.
Got another one with no student ID.
Call his parents.
-As I said, I don't go here.
-Yeah, exactly.
Do you know who I am?
I'm the head of security.
I own this place.
-I just wanted to…
-Don't move. Stay quiet. Don't even blink.
We have to stop.
Call the police.
Shouldn't I call his parents first--
The police!
Sorry.
Let's go.
Hello?
-Let's try the library first.
-Yes, totally.
Let's look through the student register.
Ben, Chris, you check the yearbooks.
-Sure.
-Okay.
Crazy, just look at all those photos.
My aunt must be in here.
-With super thin eyebrows.
-For sure.
Look, it's my dad.
Crazy. How did it go?
Did you speak to him?
It was really weird.
I know he's my dad, but…
-But it's like I don't even know him.
-Yes.
And Jonas has been stressing
the whole time.
My parents didn't even meet here
at Heartville, you know?
I think you should talk to him.
You won't get this chance again.
If we don't talk to anyone,
it will look suspicious.
Yes, it…
-It would be a waste not to talk to him.
-Exactly.
-I'll never be here again.
-Yes.
It would be a shame
to not get to know her.
"Her"?
Him.
Well… I heard "her."
No.
No. Him.
Do we even know if Charlie
is a man or a woman?
No idea. Have you noticed how all students
here look like they're in their thirties?
It's the look. Hairstyles, outfits.
In our time, old people look like that.
My dad still has the same haircut
from when he got his license.
My dad wears a fanny pack unironically.
Hey, guys. What's that sound?
It sounds like someone is torturing Siri.
Hey, crazy. They already have computers.
Double-click it.
-Guys, look here.
-Okay.
-Dude!
-Okay. Let's get online.
-Yes, Google, right?
-Yes.
-What?
-Excuse me? It's my turn.
Just a moment. There must be
a database with names.
-On the university server.
-Did you reserve a slot?
-Three minutes. Really.
-Go to the "My Computer" icon.
Did you reserve a slot?
Okay, okay. No need to be so loud.
Guys, we'll do it without the Internet.
Here's a Charlie Cane.
Here's a Charlie Conrady,
Charlie Cress, Charlie Casas.
It could be any of them.
We've got nine names.
One of them must be Charlie C.
Not much time, but let's be inconspicuous.
Why do we always build brilliant
things that we can barely carry?
-My arms are killing me right now.
-Yeah, mine, too.
Damn, I left the copies
of the presentation in the library.
Maybe the creep from the radio was right,
and we do need a camera,
-so we can pass as a film crew.
-Why not ask for a red carpet?
-Totally inconspicuous.
-That's not a bad idea.
That's what I'm saying. I'll get us one.
Oh, sorry.
Hey, Ben.
Hi, Mary Jane.
-Do you need help?
-Yes! Could you?
Sure.
Careful.
You go to the seminar room.
I'll get the copies from the library.
Okay.
-Sorry.
-What are you doing?
I'll be back in ten minutes.
He knows that time is running out, right?
-What are they doing here?
-They're ahead of us, unfortunately.
Because you distracted me
from playing beer pong yesterday.
-And that's bad?
-Yes.
It is.
Since our presentation
is now right after lunch.
And?
Well, Jamie says…
the jury will be digesting their food
and will be tired.
-That does suck.
-Yes.
Sure.
-Can I make it up to you somehow.
-Can you?
-I could buy you lunch.
-So I'll be tired as well?
You can't study
on an empty stomach, right?
2:00?
-Okay.
-Ben? Could you leave now?
We need to work.
Hi, Jamie. Nice to see you, too.
-Now.
-Yes.
Sorry.
Right.
Here are the copies of the presentation.
And then there was something else
I wanted to discuss with you…
It's right here on page two.
-So, here…
-Yes? Keep talking.
-With…
-What?
And here, look.
Can I help you?
-I didn't see you.
-It's okay. I can't see very well either.
I'm Dolly. How can I help you?
I need a camera,
but I don't know which one.
Are you looking for something specific?
Yes, I'll have a look.
Good choice. This is the first
MiniDV camera in the world.
-Perfect.
-Yes. You'll need something for sound.
This device can record
and play back. Two in one.
Crazy. That's right.
Hi, Olivia. Are you returning the camera?
Did you take nice photos?
Everything okay?
Good.
You gave me hard time
over a borrowed camera?
-I thought it was yours.
-It was mine then.
Now…
-Name?
-Oliver.
-Department?
-Film studies.
Film studies? I've never seen you there.
-I'm making a documentary.
-Nobody watches them.
I love documentaries.
In the future, everyone will watch
documentaries. Especially real crime.
That sounds weird, but it doesn't
surprise me coming from you.
I just need your student ID,
and then nothing stands
in the way of your Oscar, right?
Yes, Oliver. Where's your student ID?
Well…
Surely I can come by later with it?
Of course, my dear.
So nice.
I don't know if that's allowed,
you rascal.
Okay, then thank you so much.
Ciao.
Bye, Olivia.
Well, he's going to be famous.
Or he'll be put behind bars.
I think this time it was a bit better,
but I say let's do it again.
It's lunchtime.
I think I should maybe get…
Here. I brought lunch,
so we can keep practicing.
Okay. I have the feeling that the argument
for point four should be more concise.
I'll just get something to drink.
My throat is dry.
Especially when representing
qubits and their statuses…
I want something fizzy.
You want to stop now?
But we're really on a roll.
-Come.
-What took you so long?
It wasn't that easy.
Now let's go and find Charlie C.
-Yes. Let's go.
-Do you think it will take long?
It won't take that long.
We only have 4.5 hours left.
-Why are you asking? Got plans?
-No, I was just asking.
-Come on. We don't have much time.
-Two pics each.
Good luck finding the song. Ready?
Let's go.
Charlie Casas?
Are you Charlie Cress?
-Are you Charlie Clint?
-Yes.
Did you submit a song to Campus Radio?
No, I don't even make music.
No.
Okay, sorry.
-Charlie Chester?
-Are you Charlie Clark?
Did you submit a song to Campus Radio?
Sounds great. Keep going.
Just one.
-Sure?
-Yes.
Okay.
-Get me higher.
-I'm trying.
-No.
-No?
-That's our last Charlie C.
-Ladies.
Out of the way, dude.
Charlie Crawford?
Sorry, guys.
I don't sign autographs during training.
-Autograph? Are you nuts?
-Are you serious?
Dude, Charlie's gonna be
an All-Star one day.
-We just have a question.
-He doesn't do interviews. Get lost.
The guy is so clueless, dude.
Hey! We know your song was played
on Campus Radio yesterday.
Charlie C.
A cassette?
What are you doing?
Sorry.
-How did you even find me?
-Your name was on the tape.
-So, what do you want?
-The tape.
Sorry, you've got the wrong guy.
Wait, it isn't your song?
I'm an athlete. As if I'd ever make music.
-Nonsense.
-I get it!
The song is about you.
You're the guy who cheated.
I have a reputation to maintain.
And…
if you're smart,
then you'll forget all about this.
Charlie!
If you tell anyone
that the song is about me…
I'll kick your ass.
Great.
Now what?
We need to find Charlie's ex.
The one who wrote the song about him.
Sorry, guys, I need to use the bathroom.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-Sorry I'm late.
-No, it's fine.
-I got us some lunch.
-Nice.
-Can I have one?
-Yes, sure.
Thanks.
-Is this…
-Where did you get that?
You dropped it earlier.
But your lyrics, they are…
You read them?
Your fault. You were late.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, too,
that I looked through it. And, hey…
I really like your lyrics.
-Really?
-Yes.
Yes, they're really great.
Maybe a little too…
-No, never mind.
-Too complex?
No.
A bit too forced.
I've heard that before.
Sorry. I…
I shouldn't have read them.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
Why are you studying computer science?
Instead of music?
-Why?
-It just seems like…
Like you experience music differently
than everyone else.
No, it's just a hobby.
Just a hobby?
Maybe a bit more.
-And what's your excuse?
-My excuse?
Yes, your excuse.
For years, Jamie and I have had
this plan about computer science and…
all the things we'd like
to do together after college.
I don't even know if that's still my plan.
But… it would feel
like I was letting her down
if I suddenly decided
to do something else.
And what if your plan has changed?
What's your excuse?
My excuse?
I tried it. Music, that is.
It didn't work out the way I imagined.
The pressure just got to be too much.
What pressure do you mean?
The pressure I put on myself.
To be perfect in everything I do.
In the end, I…
I no longer felt anything
when I made music.
I realized I had missed
a lot of what was going on around me.
And that I had been ignoring people.
Sounds like you thought that you had
to sacrifice everything to make music.
Basically.
But maybe…
it's the other way around.
What you've missed out on in life is
what you need to be able to make music.
Do you know what I mean?
Just try not wanting anything for a while.
Hi.
Hey, Oli! What about your student ID?
Stop!
Out of my way.
-Stop!
-Come get me!
Stop!
I told you to…
All right…
Okay.
Get out.
-No, piss off. Please leave.
-Just a moment.
-Why are you here?
-Please!
-Open the door.
-And why?
Are you alone?
Just forget everything I said.
I just wanted to provoke you. I swear.
You can't open the door.
He'll kill me. Please.
Is someone in there?
It's okay. I'm on my own.
-Okay, buddy. I'll find you.
-Okay.
Thanks.
It's okay.
Okay. Are these all yours?
Yes.
Cool.
They're beautiful.
But that's plagiarism.
That's your photo, asshole.
I'm not passing it off as mine.
I want it back.
It's part of my project now.
I think you probably just want…
to have a little memento of me.
You're so conceited.
This doesn't mean that I'm into you.
-You're not my type anyway.
-Oh, really?
You've got a type?
Like anyone with a pulse?
Jamie? You're up.
Jamie.
-We really need to start.
-Yes.
Here you are.
You want to become a doctor?
Well, I wouldn't say "want to."
My dad is also a doctor.
-Really?
-Yes.
I have no idea how to tell him
that I'd prefer to make music.
Your dad decided to be a parent, right?
-Yes.
-Then it's his job to listen.
-What's your name again?
-Chris.
First you play D major.
D major.
Then G.
-Just a bit longer.
-I need to finish the photos. Bye.
Ciao.
And this is our auditorium.
They want to completely modernize it.
Cool, right?
Here.
It's not perfect yet.
It's just a draft.
-The end isn't quite right yet.
-Never mind, just play it.
All of this time
Make it…
Make it all make sense
I'm going higher and higher
From Earth into space
It's an existential searching
How it hurts
But you know we gotta make it work
We gotta make it work
-As you can tell, it's not quite…
-It's really good.
Can I try something?
You started by…
-I started here.
-With F. Okay.
-It's really good.
-That was completely different.
Maybe just a little less… intellectual.
-Touché.
-Come on, try it again.
All of this time
Make it all make sense
I'm going round and round
In circles again
It's an existential searching
How it hurts
But you know we gotta make…
You're still trying to do it perfectly.
Now put the notebook away and…
You've got this.
Just see where the music takes you.
-Okay.
-But wait a minute.
-This helps me sometimes.
-What's that supposed to be?
Now, we'll do one…
just…
for us, okay?
First you take my notebook away,
and now you want to record me?
Ready?
Ready.
Okay.
If I could turn back time
And relive these crazy memories
Back to the people that we used to be
Travel there with me
If we could turn back the clock
Someone tell me where we're gonna go
Open the curtain to a world
That we've been dreaming of
I wish we had more time together.
But we do.
Again?
No!
-Shit!
-Is everything okay?
I forgot about the presentation. Shit.
Jamie is gonna kill me.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
-Good luck.
-Thank you.
If I could take us right back
Back from here to the start
The look you gave me
By the end of the party
by the end of the party…
-I think I want to stay here.
-What?
-Are you crazy?
-It's so different for me here.
-Yes, it's the '90s.
-No, not because of that.
I just feel free for the first time.
With my music. With Mary Jane.
-Okay, great. He's in love.
-This can't be happening.
Bro, this isn't some kind
of self-discovery trip to Bali.
I know that.
-What happened with Mary Jane?
-Nothing.
I see, you just want to stay
to watch some MTV?
No.
We played some music together
and then we kissed.
You made out with her?
I told you not to make out with anyone.
Ben, really. That's not okay.
So embarrassing.
-Not cool, bro.
-You know what? I'm not even mad.
-I'm just disappointed.
-Come on, guys.
Wait a minute.
There's that basketball player
in the background. Charlie Crawford with…
-That's Mary Jane, right?
-Yes.
Are they a couple? They're fighting.
-100%. I can see that.
-Yes, right?
-They're not a good match.
-Hang on.
Mary Jane wrote that song
about Charlie Crawford.
-What? They were a couple?
-As if.
No way!
Yes, exactly.
Charlie C. cheated on Mary Jane.
They can't control their balls.
And she wrote a song
to process the breakup.
So, the song is about Charlie Crawford.
Then she submitted it to Submission Hour.
And, as we saw,
the song was well received
and that was somehow too much for her,
so she stole it back.
It was stolen. Breakup song
They must've regretted it.
Mary Jane must have the song on tape.
-Could be.
-Yes, dude. Totally.
Dude, that's the tape. Why didn't you say?
"Charlie C." We've got it.
-Let's go home.
-Yes.
-Yes!
-Yes, cool.
-We're going to make it.
-How cool is that?
-Perfect, let's…
-Wait.
-What is that?
-That's not the song.
-Ben, why is your voice on the tape?
-This can't be happening.
Dreaming of
Did you really destroy
our only chance to get back home?
-I didn't do it on purpose.
-You just said you wanted to stay.
-Was this your plan?
-Did you think we'd be okay staying here?
How was I supposed to know
the song would be taped over?
-Bullshit!
-Exactly the song that we need, huh?
Or you wanted to keep us here. To have
a happy ending with your retro love.
Thanks.
We're all screwed because of you.
Thanks for nothing.
Guys, please. Just wait.
We'll never get back home now.
Wait a minute.
What was it that you said?
"Nothing you hear
will show you the way."
"Only what remains will."
"Silent and abundant."
"What sounds devoid of truth
moves nothing forward."
"And nothing will succeed."
"Only what you truly feel and show
opens doors that others don't know."
So, you mean,
we just need a song that's…
That's real?
No. You need a pan flute solo.
Of course, that's what I mean.
I've got it.
Yes, I've got it.
Mary Jane wrote the song
about Charlie Crawford.
Mary Jane wrote the song.
Oh, my…
Jamie! How did it go?
Did you get the funding?
-Yes.
-Cool!
Have you heard the latest?
I shouldn't have let you down.
I know you have big plans for us,
but my heart just isn't in it right now.
The song by Mary Jane was about Charlie C.
Mary Jane wrote it.
Mary Jane's song was about Charlie C.
They were dating.
I want to study music.
For real.
It's taken you long enough!
I've been waiting forever for you
to tell me what you really want.
Do you remember our favorite song?
I know who wrote it. More importantly,
who the song is about.
I like your song.
I still hear you
In the midnight air
Your voice is the wind
It's the sound…
Oh, shit, that's my song.
Nobody was meant to know that I wrote it.
It doesn't matter. You're so talented.
Oh, my God.
Hey. A computer science student
with a voice like that? Everyone loves it.
Let me tell you.
We need to do a whole show.
With only songs by Mary Jane.
Drift through the night, through the dark
Where we used to be
Guys!
What does he want now?
There you are. I know how we can
get back home. Come with me.
-None of us want to go with you.
-Just trust me. Just this once.
I'll explain everything.
-And if he's right?
-Okay, come on. Let's go!
-Oli? Who are they?
-We have to go.
-Johnny, get them!
-Run!
No, Daniel! Don't get in!
Mary Jane.
-Guys, get in.
-We have to go.
-Come!
-Ben, that's enough. Get in.
Come on now!
See you later, okay?
You're right.
See you later.
No matter what happens now,
you should know that I'm really sorry.
I behaved like an idiot.
My obsession for everything to be perfect
made me forget what matters.
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay, bro.
-We're all idiots sometimes.
-Not everyone.
-Thanks, Ben.
-Come here.
Oh, guys…
I love you guys.
So, what's the plan?
This should work.
-The janitor said…
-Wait, what janitor?
Never mind. We don't need
that one special song.
Just a song that was created
with true feeling.
Ben, we only have seconds,
but take your time.
We just need a song that's real.
The song I recorded
with Mary Jane is more than real.
-It should work.
-Should?
Or we'll crash with the elevator.
Great. I'd rather stay here than die.
-You want to live without your phone?
-Damn. Good point.
-Okay, let's go.
-Let's try.
Okay, play.
What?
Shit!
Oh, my God!
Travel there with me
If we could turn back the clock
Someone tell me where we're gonna go
Open a curtain to a world
That we've been dreaming of
Oh, my God. My phone's working again.
-Yes!
-We're back in the present.
-Oh, my God.
-Thank God.
And… And we're 5G again.
It's kind of empty here, isn't it?
That's right,
the showcase is on right now.
Then let's perform.
What do you mean?
-We don't even have a song.
-You said the song is shit.
We've got a new song.
Come with me.
The back entrance!
Quick, run!
Shit! The showcase is over.
Never mind, go in.
…and someone might be
cheering much louder than everyone else.
Before we find out who won, we need
the woman who'll make the decision.
The woman with the baton…
Okay, Ms. Robinson can come on stage now.
-It's our turn to perform now.
-No, the showcase is over.
-No, but…
-Ms. Robinson!
-Shall we?
-Sure. Let's go.
-There's another act?
-There shouldn't be.
We're 5G.
And this is our song, "1995."
If we could turn back time
And relive these crazy memories
Back to the people that we used to be
Travel there with me
If we could turn back the clock
Someone tell me where the years have gone
Open the curtain to a world
That we've been dreaming of
If we could turn back time
Back when we were all together
Day and night
Talking and laughing
Dreaming how it would be
If we ever made it
If we could turn back time
All those years
In just a blink of our eyes
Embracing friends for life
And making up for the time we wasted
Was it so far back?
Have we been gone too long?
If I could take you right back
Back from here to the start
We'd party all night
In the back of the car
Life was totally instinctual
Fear was invisible
Didn't we have it all?
In 1995
If I could take you right back
Back from here to the start
We'd party all night
In the back of the car
Life was totally instinctual
Fear was invisible
Didn't we have it all?
In 1995
That was really cool.
Ms. Robinson.
Excuse me.
We shouldn't have performed.
But we gave it our all.
The song…
is really close to my heart.
I know that, Ben.
I wrote that song with you.
I just had to come back.
Maybe we were meant to meet each other.
Maybe we needed each other.
Maybe this is a second chance.
Some things just belong
in the moment they happened.
But you showed me that love exists.
That remains.
Even if you have to let it go.
I just wish we could have spent
more time together.
A heart heals, Ben.
Not right away…
but it puts itself back together again.
And keeps beating…
Stronger than before.
I've seen many fantastic,
talented artists today.
But talent alone is not enough.
It takes courage to go your own way.
Dad.
Come here. I'm so proud of you.
Sometimes, we're so focused on our goal
that we forget what truly drives us.
You're not mad at me?
Why?
About the interview with Mehackerberg?
The letter?
I think you need to calm down first.
You're a little flustered.
Life should inspire art.
Not the other way around.
Those who don't experience anything
have nothing to share.
And I saw that courage
in someone today.
Someone who was willing to open up
and show themselves.
Without fear.
But with real passion.
That's why I'd like
to give Skyler the chance she deserves.
You know what's great about this morning?
It's not that the birds are singing.
It's the fact that we didn't have
to bring any pink sprinkles.
I knew you'd say that.
You know what else is great? For once
being well-rested for a rehearsal.
Yes. Do you know why?
Because we finally got enough sleep.
I'm happy that Ben doesn't kick in
the door like a SWAT team anymore.
You used to really freak out
when we weren't here by 6:00 a.m.
-Don't exaggerate.
-Exaggerate?
You once texted me at 3:00 a.m.
reminding me to learn my lyrics.
With a skull emoji.
-I just wanted to motivate you.
-More like "manipulate."
But honestly, Ben,
you're so relaxed now,
it's almost pleasant.
I don't know what you mean.
I have always been very relaxed.
-Yes! 100%.
-Look me in the eyes and say that again.
I've just always been very committed.
A follower just sent me a link to a TikTok
account full of cool vintage B-sides.
-Don't!
-Oli, stop!
Slate 2, take 2.
We don't get involved with anyone,
we don't "pefriend" anyone.
Sorry.
The rules are as follows.
I'm sorry, I can't…
Action.
I was startled there.
Jonas, open the door.
It's Ben. Go again.
It's always the same.
-On the mark.
-I'm not on the mark?
I'll start over…
Well, when I heard… Shit!
-Forgot the line.
-I returned it though.
Sorry.
What did you say? "She should piss off?
Kiss my ass?"
-She should piss off.
-Kids.
Hello, you.
You just hit me in the face so hard.
-How's it going?
-It's not a talk show.
-Makeup?
-Where have you been?
-In the bathroom.
-How was it?
-Smooth.
-Great. And we're smoothly moving on.
The nudist beach?
Yes, but…
Have I forgotten anything?
Okay, Charlie is tired.
-What's that?
-It's my Tamagotchi.
And cut.